Guide to the Todd-Bingham Picture Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- PHOTOGRAPHS, Circa 1850s-1966; Series I; 16 linear feet (37 boxes)
  - Astronomy and astronomers
    - Observations
      - Mars (Box 35, Folder 358)
      - Moon (Box 35, Folder 359)
      - Nebulae (Box 35, Folder 360)
      - Transit of Venus (Box 35, Folder 361)
    - Observatories
      - Australia: New South Wales (?) (Box 36, Folder 362)
      - Germany: Treptow—Sternwarte Observatory, Berlin (Box 36, Folder 363)
      - Peru
        - Arequipa: Boyden Observatory (Box 36, Folder 364)
        - Chosica: Mount Harvard Observatory (Box 36, Folder 365)
      - United States
        - California: Lick Observatory, Mt. Hamilton (Box 36, Folder 366)
        - Massachusetts
          - Amherst
            - Lawrence Observatory ("Old Observatory") (Box 36, Folder 367)
            - "New Observatory"
              - Construction (Box 36, Folder 368)
              - Views (Box 36, Folder 369)
          - Northampton: Smith College Observatory (Box 36, Folder 370)
          - Wellesley: Whitin Observatory (Box 36, Folder 371)
      - New York: Warner Observatory, Rochester (Box 36, Folder 372)
      - Washington, D.C.: U.S. Naval Observatory (Box 36, Folder 373)
      - Wisconsin: Yerkes Observatory, Williams Bay (Box 36, Folder 374)
      - Unidentified (Box 36, Folder 375)
  - Artwork
    - European artworks—prints (Box 37, Folder 376-377)
    - Sketches (Box 37, Folder 378)
- ALBUMS AND SCRAPBOOKS, [ca1860s-1917]; Series II; 5 linear feet (14 boxes)
  This series contains photograph and post card albums, loose album pages, and miscellaneous albums. This material is arranged in the following six sections: Loomis-Wilder Family, Todd Family, Millicent Todd Bingham, David Peck Todd, Mabel Loomis Todd, and Miscellaneous.
  Albums are numbered consecutively 1-32 with loose album pages assigned only box numbers (47-49). An approximate chronological arrangement within each section has been attempted, although the inconsistent dating of photographs and the diversity of topics within albums prevents such an arrangement from being exact.
  Related photographs are arranged in other series under appropriate sections.
  - Loomis-Wilder Family
    - Album no. 1
      This album contains photographs for members and friends of the Loomis-Wilder family in the Washington, D.C. area. These photographs date from the late 1860s and 1870s. An incomplete list of the individuals includes:
      - Ammidon, Fred and Russel (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Cutter family (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Gardner, Clarence (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Loomis, Nathan (tintype) (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Wilder, Mary Wales Fobes Jones (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Wilder, John Augustus (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Album no. 2
      This album contains photographs of members of the Loomis-Wilder family and several unidentified individuals. Included in this volume are:
      - Ammidon, Philip A. (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Hawthorne, Nathan (?) (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Loomis, Eben Jenks (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Loomis, George C. (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Loomis, Mary Alden Wilder (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Todd, Mabel Loomis (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Wilder, John Augustus (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Wilder, Mary Wales Fobes Jones (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Todd Family (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Album no. 3
      This album contains photographs of the Todd family and friends from the 1880s. Among the individuals and views are:
      - Compton, Naomi Todd (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Cutter, Everett (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Dickinson, Lavinia Norcross (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Loomis, Eben Jenks (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Loomis, Mary Alder Wilder (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Newcomb family (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Stearns, Mrs. W. F. (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Todd, David Peck (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Todd, Mabel Loomis (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Todd—residence: 1413 College Hill Terrace, Amherst, Massachusetts (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Todd—residence: "The Dell" (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Todd—residence: "Lessez House(?)" (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Album no. 4
      This album contains photographs of a variety of subjects and individuals from 1903-1904. Topics in this album include:
      Aloha cruise, 1903: a New England journey from Newport, Rhode Island; Provincetown, Massachusetts; Portsmouth, New Hampshire; Northeast Harbor, Maine
      - Children, unidentified (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Concord, Massachusetts (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - East Aurora, Illinois (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Milinowski family (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - St. Louis, Missouri (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Unidentified (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Album no. 5
      This album contains photographs of outdoor views and of individuals photographed in Amherst, Massachusetts, ca.1903. Included here are:
      - Amherst, Massachusetts: winter scenes (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Children (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Daughters of the American Revolution (D.A.R.): building, members, events (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Todd, David Peck (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Album no. 6 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      This album contains photographs of the island of Bermuda as well as several photographs of buildings and scenes in Fairhaven, Massachusetts, ca. 1905-1906.
    - Album no. 7 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      This album includes photographs, both purchased and personally taken, by members of the Todd family, ca. 1904. Individuals seen here are Eben Jenks Loomis and Mary Alder Wilder Loomis.
    - Album no. 8 (Box 40, Folder 8)
      Numerous scenes of the buildings and geography of Florida, ca. 1910s, are found here, with members of the Todd family included in many of the photographs.
    - Album no. 9 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      Hog Island, Muscongas Bay, Maine, is the location for photograph in this album, dated 1910-1911. Family members are shown at many buildings and sites on the island which was later donated designated a wildlife sanctuary in 1935.
      See also: box 41
    - Album no. 10 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      Two major sections divide this album, first, photographs of Eben Jenks Loomis' visit to Florida with Herbert Wilder in 1911 and second, the visit of David Peck Todd and Mabel Loomis Todd to the home of Arthur Curtis James in Coconut Grove, Florida, 1917-1918.
    - Album no. 11 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      Hog Island, Muscongas Bay, Maine, this time in the year 1912, is shown in several photographs. Included here are Millicent Todd Bingham and other family members.
      See also: box 40
    - Album no. 12 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      This album of negatives has been refoldered for preservation. purposes. The negatives, with numerical index, illustrate Florida and Cuba, ca. 1918.
    - Album no. 13 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      This album holds miscellaneous photographs of Florida, ca. 1910-1920.
  - Millicent Todd Bingham
    - Album no. 14 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      This album contains numerous photographs of an 1899 trip to Europe, including scenes of France, Italy, Switzerland, and Germany.
    - Album no. 15 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      This album consists of postcards depicting scenes and performers from the Oberammergau Passionspeil, 1900.
      See also: box 69, folder 408-421
      See also: box 111-114
    - Album no. 16 (Box 42, Folder 16)
      This album contains photographs of the inhabitants, geography, buildings, and sites of Chile in 1907. Millicent Todd Bingham accompanied her parents on their astronomical expedition to Chile and apparently took the opportunity to observe the country.
    - Album no. 17 (Box 42, Folder 17)
      This album also concentrates on the nation of Chile in 1907. In addition to scenes of laborers and the countryside, there are photographs of the astronomical equipment and operations.
    - Album no. 18 (Box 42, Folder 18)
      This album focuses on two areas, Santo Domingo and Peru, where the Todd family also travelled in 1907.
  - David Peck Todd
    - Album no. 19 (Box 43)
      This album includes both prints of the eclipse of 9 August 1896, and the equipment, construction efforts, campsite, and members of the expedition. In addition, to views of the actual eclipse, there are scenes of Esashi, Japan, its residents, and surrounding area.
      See also: box 166
    - Album no. 20 and Scrapbook (Box 44, Folder 20)
      "New Amherst College Observatory, Vol. I," is composed of clippings, photographs, and correspondence dating 1897-1902, which document the construction of the Amherst College Observatory.
    - Album no. 21 and Scrapbook (Box 44, Folder 21)
      "New Amherst College Observatory, Vol. II," is composed of clippings, photographs, and correspondence dating 1903-1907, which document the construction and opening of the observatory.
    - Album no. 22 (Box 44, Folder 22)
      "Building of Amherst College Observatory," is composed of photographs, [ca. 1903 May—1905 June], which illustrate the construction and opening of the observatory.
    - Album no. 23 (Box 45, Folder 23)
      "New Amherst College Observatory," is composed of negatives of photographs found in several albums, including volumes 21-22. These negatives have been refoldered for preservation purposes.
    - Album no. 24 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Mabel Loomis Todd
    - Album no. 25
      This album contains "minette" photographs of several friends of Mabel Loomis Todd from Boston, Massachusetts, and possibly other locations. This list of friends includes:
      - Cutler family (Box 45, Folder 25)
      - Hocer, Mary (Box 45, Folder 25)
      - Lovejoy, Emma (Box 45, Folder 25)
      - Mason, Nellie (Box 45, Folder 25)
      - Stearns, Sue C. (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - Album no. 26
      This album includes minature tintypes of several early friends of Mabel Loomis Todd and of "Mabel Loomis This list of friends includes:
      - Ammidon family (Box 45, Folder 26)
      - Bruce family (Box 45, Folder 26)
      - Cutler, Maria (Box 45, Folder 26)
      - Gardner, E. C. (Box 45, Folder 26)
      - Mason family (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - Album no. 27
      This album was presented to Mabel Loomis by her grandmother Mary Wales Fobes Jones Wilder in 1888. Among the family and friends included here are:
      - Ammidon family (Box 46, Folder 27)
      - Bispham family (Box 46, Folder 27)
      - Compton, Naomi (Box 46, Folder 27)
      - Holland family (Box 46, Folder 27)
      - Loomis, Mary Alder Wilder (Box 46, Folder 27)
      - Newcomb family (Box 46, Folder 27)
      - Sage family (Box 46, Folder 27)
      - Todd, David Peck (Box 46, Folder 27)
      - Todd, Mabel Loomis (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Album no. 28 (Box 46, Folder 28)
      This album contains professionally produced prints of the Panama Canal and its construction.
    - Album no. 29 (Box 46, Folder 29)
      This album includes photographs taken on a trip to Los Angeles, California, ca. 1905, apparently en route to a convention of women's clubs. Scenes of Ogden, Utah, Los Angeles, California; and Denver, Colorado are included.
    - Album pages
      Photographs are mounted on the front and back of cardboard sheets. Topics highlighted here include:
      - Hampton, New Hampshire, 1895 (Box 47)
      - Vassar College, 1897-1902; 1903-1904 (Box 47)
      - Hancock Point, 1903-1904 (Box 47)
      - Algiers, 1901 (Box 47)
      - Japan, 1901 (Box 47)
      - Alohacruise, 1903 (Box 47)
      - Middlebrook, New Hampshire, 1902 (Box 47)
    - Album pages
      Photographs are mounted on the front and back of Cardboard sheets. Topics highlighted here include:
      - Wellesley College, 1906-1907 (Box 48)
      - Paris, France, 1906 (Box 48)
      - Galgarish (?), undated (Box 48)
      - Soudan, undated (Box 48)
      - Tripoli, 1905 (Box 48)
      - Naples, Italy, 1905 (Box 48)
      - Malta, 1905 (Box 48)
    - Album pages
      - Peru, 1907 (Box 49)
      - Chile, 1907 (Box 49)
      - Panama, 1907 (Box 49)
      - Amherst, Massachusetts, 1908-1909 (Box 49)
      - Germany, 1909-1910 (Box 49)
      - Maine, 1919-1911; 1912 (Box 49)
      - Santa Monica, California, undated (Box 49)
      - Aloha, 1914 (Box 49)
      - Kiev, Russia, 1914 (Box 49)
      - Canada, 1915 (Box 49)
      - Vassar College, 1915 (Box 49)
      - Miscellaneous, 1915-1917 (Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Album no. 30 (Box 50, Folder 30)
      This album contains a series of postcards from Russia (Kiev, St. Petersburgh, Moscow), Finland, and England.
    - Album no. 31 (Box 51, Folder 31)
      This album was formerly the property of Mrs. Mary E. (William French) Stearns. It contains photographs, by "Bourne," of scenes in India ca. 1860s(?).
    - Album no. 32 (Box 51A, Folder 32)
      This album contains color prints of Japanese scenes by an unknown photographer.
- GLASS NEGATIVES AND LANTERN SLIDES, [ca1870s-1910]; Series III; 17 linear feet (121 boxes)
  This series is arranged in six sections: Glass negatives, Lantern slides, Oversize, Prints, Film negatives, and Folios.
  There are approximately 1,000 standard size glass negatives (4"x 5"; 5"x 7"). They are arranged in the following sub-sections: Todd family; Todd family friends; Todd family friends—groups and places; Africa, North; Africa, South; Africa, West; Chile; Dutch East Indies; Ecuador; Germany; India; Japan; Peru;. Philippines; Russia; Spain; United States: West Indies; and Astronomy and textbook material. Each negative is numbered consecutively, to correspond to those photographic prints arranged and numbered in parallel sub-sections in the Prints section.
  Lantern slides contains 1,187 items. It is arranged in sub-sections similar to those for Glass negatives. Lantern slides' subsections are: Africa, North; Africa, South; Africa, West; Chile; Dutch East Indies; Egypt; Germany; Japan; Panama; Russia; Siam; Spain; Sweden; United States; West Indies; and Astronomy and texbook material. Each slide is consecutively numbered, to correspond to those photographic prints arranged and numbered in parallel sub-sections in the Prints section.
  Oversize consists of large glass negatives (6 1/2"x 8 1/2"; 8"x 10"; 10"x 12"; 12" x 15"). These items are numbered as if arranged in the sequence of glass negatives, with cross-reference citations to this section (boxes 159-167). Oversize includes negatives 1141-1161, which are not listed in the Glass negatives section. These items were not originally maintained with the smaller sized negatives and were identified and numbered after the first 1140 negatives were described.
  Prints contains positive photographic prints of selected glass negatives and lantern slides. Each print is numbered to correspond to its glass negative or lantern slide.
  Film negatives consists of 35mm negatives of selected lantern slides (those with positive prints in the section Prints). These negatives are arranged in parallel sub-sections to the lantern slides.
  Due to the presence of numerous negatives on each film sheet, the geographic division of the negatives is not mutually exclusive and cross-references are provided.
  The following numbered negatives are missing from the Glass negatives section, as they were in a state of deterioration which rendered them useless: 144-146, 821, and 1,106. The following numbered slides are missing from the Lantern slides section, as they were also in an advanced state of deterioration: 46-47, and 620.
  Folios contains the glass negatives too large for oversized boxes.
  - Glass Negatives
    - Todd family
      - Unidentified woman (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Todd, Mabel Loomis (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Bingham, Millicent Todd, "Plates of myself in Lombards Gardens", 1919 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Bingham, Millicent Todd, "Plates of myself in Lombards Gardens", 1919 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Bingham, Millicent Todd, "Plates of myself in Lombards Gardens", 1919 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Todd family friends
      - A-C (Box 52, Folder 6-10)
      - Dickinson, Emily (Box 52, Folder 11-14)
      - Dickinson, Gilbert (Box 52, Folder 15-16)
      - Dickinson, William Austin (Box 53, Folder 17-19)
        See: box 159
      - H—T (Box 53, Folder 20-32)
      - Stearns family
        - Stearns, A. E. (Box 53, Folder 33)
        - Stearns, Alfred (Box 53, Folder 34-35)
        - Stearns, Annie (Box 53, Folder 36-39)
        - Stearns, Arthur (and the Ayala) (Box 53, Folder 40-41)
        - Stearns, Ethel (Box 53, Folder 42-43)
        - Stearns, Frazar (Box 53, Folder 44-46)
        - Stearns, Harold (Box 54, Folder 47)
        - "Stearns," Samuel (Box 54, Folder 48)
        - Stearns, "Willi" (Box 54, Folder 49-54)
        - "President Stearns" (Box 54, Folder 55)
        - Mrs. Stearns(?) (Box 54, Folder 56-57)
        - Stearns—"Earliest married life" (Box 54, Folder 58-60)
        - Stearns—children (Box 54, Folder 61-65)
      - Unidentified (Box 54, Folder 66-67)
      - Unidentified (Box 55, Folder 68-70)
    - Todd family friends—groups and places
      - Mrs. Emerson(?) and David Peck Todd (Box 55, Folder 71-72)
      - Kirby family—children (Box 55, Folder 73)
      - Stearns family—children (Box 55, Folder 74-79)
      - Stearns family—general
        - Francistown, New Hampshire (Box 55, Folder 80-81)
        - Mount Vernon, New Hampshire (Box 55, Folder 82-85)
        - Unidentified (Box 55, Folder 86-89)
      - Stearns family—miscellaneous
        - "Mary and Alfred in canoe,", 1910 June 28 (Box 55, Folder 90)
        - "Hal Stearns, two children,", 1901 June 10 (Box 55, Folder 91)
    - Africa, North
      - Tripoli, 1900
        - General (Box 56, Folder 92-109)
        - General (Box 57, Folder 110-128)
        - Eclipse expedition (Box 57, Folder 129-133)
        - Eclipse expedition—oversize (Box 57, Folder 134)
        - People (Box 57, Folder 135-142)
        - People—oversize (Box 57, Folder 143)
        - People—negatives missing (Box 57, Folder 144-145)
      - Tripoli, 1905
        - General—negative missing (Box 58, Folder 146)
        - General (Box 58, Folder 147-168)
        - General (Box 59, Folder 169-182)
          See also: box 48
        - General (Box 59, Folder 183-200)
        - General (Box 59, Folder 201)
        - Eclipse expedition (Box 60, Folder 202-203)
        - Eclipse expedition (Box 60, Folder 204-208)
        - Todd, David Peck (Box 60, Folder 209)
        - Todd, Millicent Bingham (Box 60, Folder 210-213)
    - Africa, South
      - Capetown, 1899 (Box 60, Folder 214)
    - Africa, West
      - Angola, 1889 (Box 60)
      - General (Box 60, Folder 215-225)
      - Eclipse expedition
        - Coronas (Box 61, Folder 226-243)
        - Coronas (Box 62, Folder 244-255)
        - Coronas (Box 62, Folder 256)
          See: box 164
        - Instruments (Box 62, Folder 257-259)
        - "Pensacola" cruise (Box 63, Folder 260-277)
        - "Pensacola" cruise (Box 64, Folder 278-280)
        - Textbook material (Box 64, Folder 281-285)
      - Ascension Island (Box 64, Folder 286-287)
      - Azores, 1889 (Box 64, Folder 288-289)
      - Cape Ledo (Box 64, Folder 290-291)
      - Loanda, 1889 (Box 64, Folder 292-294)
      - Rio Quanzo (Box 64, Folder 295)
      - St. Helena (Box 64, Folder 296-297)
      - St. Helena (Box 65, Folder 298-315)
      - Sierra Leone (Box 65, Folder 316-17)
    - Chile
      - General (Box 66, Folder 318-331)
    - Dutch East Indies, 1901
      - Singkep
        - General (Box 66, Folder 332-347)
        - General (Box 67, Folder 348-363)
        - Eclipse expedition
          - Coronas (Box 67, Folder 364-373)
          - Stages of eclipse (Box 68, Folder 374-380)
    - Ecuador
      - General (Box 68, Folder 381-398)
      - General (Box 69, Folder 399-407)
    - Germany
      - Oberammergau Passion Play, 1900 (Box 69, Folder 408-421)
      - Oberammergau Passion Play, 1900 (Box 70, Folder 422-356)
    - India
      - Stearns negatives (Box 70, Folder 436-447)
      - Stearns negatives (Box 71, Folder 448-449)
      - Places—Bombay (Box 71, Folder 450-456)
      - Places—unidentified (Box 71, Folder 457-469)
      - People—unidentified (Box 71, Folder 470-473)
    - Japan
      - Ainu people, 1896
        - Native life (Box 72, Folder 474-480)
        - People (Box 72, Folder 481-486)
        - Oversize (Box 72, Folder 487-489)
      - Esasbi, 1896
        - General (Box 72, Folder 490)
        - People (Box 72, Folder 490-494)
        - Places—Avenue of Royal Palms (Box 72, Folder 495)
        - Places (Box 72, Folder 496-501)
        - Places—unidentified (Box 72, Folder 502-503)
        - Eclipse expedition
          - Coronas (Box 72, Folder 504-508)
          - Coronas (Box 73, Folder 509-510)
          - Coronas (Box 73, Folder 511)
          - "Coronet" cruise
            - Cruise map (Box 73, Folder 512)
            - Passengers (Box 73, Folder 513-519)
        - Instruments (Box 73)
        - Instruments (Box 73, Folder 528-536)
        - Ogawa negatives (Box 73, Folder 537-549)
        - Ogawa negatives (Box 74, Folder 550-579)
        - Site (Box 74, Folder 580-582)
        - Site (Box 74, Folder 583-603)
          See: box 160
        - Voyage, railroads, miscellaneous (Box 75, Folder 604-612)
        - Unidentified (Box 75, Folder 613-616)
      - Fuji, 1887
        - Fujiyama (Box 75, Folder 617-620)
        - Maps and diagrams (Box 75, Folder 621-629)
        - Temple grounds (Box 75, Folder 630-634)
      - Shirakawa, 1887
        - General (Box 76, Folder 635-640)
        - General (Box 76, Folder 641)
        - Textbook (Box 76, Folder 642-646)
        - Eclipse expedition
          - Campsite (Box 76, Folder 647-648)
          - Campsite (Box 76, Folder 649-651)
          - Coronas (Box 76, Folder 652-656)
          - Coronas, sketches (Box 76, Folder 657-660)
        - Coronas—booklet; "The Total Eclipse of the Sun of August 19, 1887. observed and drawn at Yominji Yama…," by Shuji Isawa, Chief of the Bureau of Compilation under the Imperial Department of Education. (Box 77, Folder 661-680)
        - Coronas—booklet (Box 78, Folder 681-699)
        - Coronas—booklet (Box 79, Folder 700-11)
        - Diagrams of eclipse route and notations (Box 79, Folder 712-714)
    - Peru
      - Native life and scenery—by Millicent Todd Bingham (Box 79, Folder 715-722)
      - Native life and scenery—by Millicent Todd Bingham (Box 80, Folder 723-735)
    - Philippines
      - Jolo (Box 80, Folder 736-739)
      - Manila (Box 80, Folder 740-749)
      - Map (Box 80, Folder 750)
    - Russia
      - Eclipse expedition (Box 80, Folder 751-760)
        See: box 164 box 165
    - Spain
      - Granada (Box 81, Folder 761-767)
    - Other nations and areas (Box 81, Folder 767)
    - Algiers (Box 81, Folder 768-770)
    - Gibraltar (Box 81, Folder 771)
    - Tunis
      - General (Box 81, Folder 772-785)
      - General (Box 82, Folder 786-794)
      - Unidentified (Box 82, Folder 795-801)
    - United States
      - California
        - House, exterior (Box 82, Folder 802)
          See: box 161
        - House, interiors (Box 82, Folder 803-807)
        - Views—sailboat (Box 82, Folder 808)
        - Views—sailboat negative destroyed (Box 82, Folder 809)
        - Views—sailboat (Box 82, Folder 810-813)
        - Views—mountainside (Box 82, Folder 814-818)
        - Views—San Francisco (Box 82, Folder 819)
      - Florida
        - Coconut Grove, Miami highway (Box 82, Folder 820)
        - Coconut Grove, Miami highway—negative missing (Box 82, Folder 821)
        - Millicent Todd Bingham negatives. (Box 82, Folder 822-826)
      - Hawaii, 1896
        - Views (Box 83, Folder 827-844)
        - Field, Kate (Box 83, Folder 845-846)
          See: box 165
      - Massachusetts
        - Amherst
          - "Convent"
            - exterior (Box 83, Folder 847)
            - students (Box 83, Folder 848)
          - Amherst Historical Society
            - exteriors (Box 83, Folder 852-853)